Jordan Perry

Hybrid Mobile Application Developer

Fayetteville, AR - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Jordan-Perry/1f4861b8f62570d0

Hybrid mobile application developer specializing in front end development. Experienced with iterative development cycle and agile methodology. Extensive knowledge of JavaScript, CSS, HTML5, and AngularJS. Adaptive to new languages and frameworks with an interest in user experience and creative design.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Programmer Analyst

WALMART Stores Incorporated - Bentonville, AR - February 2016 to Present

Develop solutions that reduced inventory by 1.5 billion dollars. Deliver hybrid mobile applications to store associates enabling the monitoring business intelligence metrics and completion store processes. Assess user feedback to tailor applications overall usability and troubleshoot potential defects.

Oversee Product Releases/ Collaboration/ Train. Plan, document, and validate releases to over 4,000 Walmart stores and over 600 Sam's Clubs. Collaborate with cross functional teams to achieve valuable, user-friendly applications. Manage the training of new developers on best practices and technology stack.

IT Rotational Analyst

WALMART Stores Incorporated - Bentonville, AR - June 2015 to February 2016

Information Security Developer. Developed security dashboard for security operations analysts to monitor realtime metrics of potential threats and malicious activity.

Innovation. Worked with dynamic defense engineers to identify problem areas in operations. Upgraded security tools by programming new features to align with operational needs. Reduced operation execution time by one-fifth.

Tutor

Kentucky State University - Frankfort, KY - February 2013 to May 2015

Responsibilities

- Administered additional assistance for students' coursework
- Provided students with helpful study techniques and mnemonics
- Created a positive environment for students to ask questions and state concerns

Skills Used

Communication, integration, and swift transitions

Research Assistant

University of Kentucky - Lexington, KY - September 2012 to May 2013

Research / Enhancement. Worked with the Agricultural Department at the University of Kentucky on plant DNA research. Integrated basic understanding of biology concepts and computer science skills to improve data on DNA makeup. Enhanced algorithms to produce more accurate representations of the plant's DNA molecules to generate additional molecule information.

EDUCATION

Computer Science

Kentucky State University - Frankfort, KY 2011 to 2015

SKILLS

Javascript, HTML5, Development, Testing, Python, Troubleshooting, C++, CSS, CQL, Visual Basic, SQL, Inventory Management, Customer Service, Teamwork, Interpersonal Skills (2 years)

AWARDS

Community Engagement

February 2017

This award was granted to my involvement with Salvation Army and multiple local charities, as well as, developing a mobile application for the Salvation Army's Angel Tree.

Outstanding Value Delivery

February 2017

This award highlights the development of mobile solutions that contributed to saving the company 1.5 billion dollars in inventory reduction.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Activities:

- -AR Girls Code, Mentor/Instructor: 2016- Present
- -Wal-mart Inc, Summer Intern Mentor: 2016
- -Alpha Kappa Mu Honor Society: 2015-Present